total-soft.pe.hu 2017-12-22

# » Privacy Policy

### .

## .

## **Limited Time Offer**

* * *

## **SPECIAL OFFER**

### Get discount when you buy all Total Soft Developer plugins worth **170 for 55 **only. It Includes Event Calendar, Poll, Portfolio Gallery, Video Gallery & Total Event Calendar.

##  Information We Collect From You 

Total-Soft servers automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us: such as your IP address, browser type and language, the date, time of your request. Total-Soft also uses “cookies” – small files containing a string of characters sent to your computer that can uniquely identifies your browser – in addition to Flash shared browser objects to administer its website to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use Total-Soft services in order to improve the quality of our services.

##  How We Use Your Information 

The information We collect is used: 1. to respond to Your inquiries; 2. to provide customer services and resolve any complaints; 3. to improve the website and service and resolve any technical problems; 4. to communicate with You concerning the services offered on the Website by Us or on any social networking sites; 5. cross-reference with other Personal Information that We have acquired about You or may acquire about You through other sources; 6. to create aggregate data; 7. to maintain a customer database which will be used for in-house business operations ; and 8. to market the products and services of our third party advertisers.

##  We Can Share Your Information In Case 

We may disclose Personal Information: 1. to companies that help process the transactions You request, in order to protect Your transactions from fraud and verify Your identity; 2. to government officials and agencies as required by law in case of illegal activities ; 3. to comply with legal, regulatory or administrative requirements of governmental authorities (including, without limitation, requests from the governmental agency authorities to view Your Personal Information); 4. to protect and defend Us in connection with any legal action, claim or dispute; 5. to prevent imminent physical harm; 6. to share aggregated statistical or demographic data with business partners or for public relations; 7. to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a bankruptcy or liquidation; and 8. to sell or otherwise provide to third parties in the event of a future merger or acquisition by another company.

##  Data Security 

Total-Soft will take appropriate security measures designed to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. Total-Soft processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. Total-Soft takes reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

If Total-Soft learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Total-Soft may post a notice on the website if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at totalsoft.team@gmail.com

##  Trademark 

The trademarks, logos, and service marks (collectively the “Trademarks”) displayed on this Web Site are registered trademarks of Total-Soft company its affiliates and others. Nothing contained on this Web Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any Trademark displayed on this Web Site without the written permission of Total-Soft company or such third party that may own the trademark displayed on this Web Site. Your misuse of the Trademarks displayed on this Web Site, or any other content on this Web Site, except as provided herein, is strictly prohibited.

##  Changes And Updates To This Privacy Notice 

By Using this Website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Any revised Privacy Policy will only apply prospectively to Personal Information collected or modified after the effective date of the revised policy.

##  Contact US About Privacy 

All our themes are licensed under the GPL general public license (see <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl.html>)

_YOU AND Total-SoftT AGREE THAT ANY CAUSE OF ACTION ARISING OUT OF OR RELATED TO THE Total-Soft SERVICE MUST COMMENCE WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES. OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION IS PERMANENTLY BARRED._
